Guide to the Portland Reporter Photographs Collection 1960-1964
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Subject Files, circa 1900-1965; 1960-1965; Series A
  - Churches
    - Icons—"Eikon" in St. David's Church, 1922 (Box-folder 11/16)
    - Jehovah's Witnesses, 1960 (Box-folder 11/17)
    - Jewish, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 11/18)
    - Jewish—Ahavath Achim, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 11/19)
    - Jewish—Ahavai Shalom, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 11/20)
    - Jewish—Beth Israel, 1963 (Box-folder 11/21)
    - Jewish—Neveh Shalom, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 11/22)
    - Jewish—Neveh Zedek, 1961 (Box-folder 11/23)
    - Jewish—Shaarie Torah, 1964 (Box-folder 11/24)
    - Latter Day Saints, 1961 (Box-folder 11/25)
    - Lutheran—Augustana, Grace, 1960; 1964 (Box-folder 11/26)
    - Lutheran—Our Savior, 1962 (Box-folder 11/27)
    - Lutheran—Prince of Peace, 1962 (Box-folder 11/28)
    - Lutheran—St. Luke, 1962 (Box-folder 11/29)
    - Lutheran—St. Stephen's, 1962 (Box-folder 11/30)
    - Lutheran—St. Timothy, 1962 (Box-folder 11/31)
    - Methodist, 1964 (Box-folder 11/32)
    - Methodist—First, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 11/33)
    - Methodist—Lake Oswego, 1964 (Box-folder 11/34)
    - Methodist—Montavilla, 1961 (Box-folder 11/35)
    - Methodist—Parkrose, undated (Box-folder 11/36)
    - Methodist—University Park, 1962 (Box-folder 11/37)
    - Methodist—Vermont Hills, undated (Box-folder 11/38)
    - Molalla, 1962 (Box-folder 11/39)
    - Open Bible, 1963 (Box-folder 11/40)
    - Presbyterian—Oak Hills, 1964 (Box-folder 11/41)
    - Presbyterian—First, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 11/42)
    - Presbyterian—St. Mark, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 11/43)
    - Presbyterian—Westminster, 1960 (Box-folder 11/44)
    - St. Thomas More, 1964 (Box-folder 11/45)
    - Seventh Day Adventist, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 11/46)
    - Unitarian—First, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 11/47)
    - Unitarian—West Hills, 1961 (Box-folder 11/48)
    - Vancouver, Wash., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 11/49)
    - West Hills Covenant, 1963 (Box-folder 11/50)
  - Circus, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 11/51)
  - Circus—Barnum and Bailey-Ringling Brothers, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 11/52)
  - Circus—Shriner's, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 11/53)
  - Circus—Wenatchee Youth, 1963 (Box-folder 11/54)
  - Cistern, 1964 (Box-folder 11/55)
  - Citizens, New, 1963 (Box-folder 11/56)
  - Civic Auditorium--Model, undated (Box-folder 11/57)
  - Civil defense, 1961 (Box-folder 11/58)
  - Civil defense-Portland, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 11/59)
  - Civil rights, 1961; 1964; undated (Box-folder 11/60)
  - Civil War reenactment--Banks, Or., 1961 (Box-folder 11/61)
  - Clackamas County Fair, 1961 (Box-folder 11/62)
  - Clackamas County Public Welfare, 1961 (Box-folder 11/63)
  - Clackamas River, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 11/64)
  - Clams, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 11/65)
  - Clark College, Vancouver, WA--Chime tower, 1964 (Box-folder 11/66)
  - Clatsop Community College, 1962 (Box-folder 11/67)
  - Cle Elum, WA, 1962 (Box-folder 11/68)
  - Clocks, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 11/69)
  - Clover Street Riding Team, 1962 (Box-folder 11/70)
  - Cloves, 1964 (Box-folder 11/71)
  - Clowns, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Clubs--Progressive Social Club, 1963 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Coast Guard, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Coca Cola, 1963 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Coins, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Cold War, undated (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Collectibles, 1964 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Colleges--Graph, 1961 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Colonial Manor, 1961 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Colony, 1961 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Columbia Christian College, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Columbia County Courthouse, 1963 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Columbia County Fair, 1963 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Columbia Edgewater County Club, 1961 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Columbia River, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Columbia River Highway construction project, 1961 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Columbia River--Pipeline, 1960 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Columbia Steel Casting Company, Inc., 1962 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - Columbia View Manor, 1961 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Community colleges, 1964 (Box-folder 12/20)
  - Concord Terrace Mobile Park, 1964 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - Congolese in Portland, 1961 (Box-folder 12/22)
  - Congress, 1963 (Box-folder 12/23)
  - Consumer Advisory Committee, 1964 (Box-folder 12/24)
  - Contest--Hawaiin holiday, 1963 (Box-folder 12/25)
  - Coos River, 1962 (Box-folder 12/26)
  - Corn, 1961 (Box-folder 12/27)
  - Cornell University, 1961 (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Corrections, wire photos, 1964 (Box-folder 12/29)
  - Cosmonauts, 1963 (Box-folder 12/30)
  - Coucil Crest (circa 1889), 1961 (Box-folder 12/31)
  - County (Multnomah) Planning Commission, 1960 (Box-folder 12/32)
  - Covered wagons, 1962 (Box-folder 12/33)
  - Cranes, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12/34)
  - Credit savers, 1962 (Box-folder 12/35)
  - Crestview Convalescent Center, 1964 (Box-folder 12/36)
  - Crickets, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 12/37)
  - Croatians, 1963 (Box-folder 12/38)
  - Crooked River Roundup, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12/39)
  - Crown Zellerbach, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12/40)
  - Crucifix, 1964 (Box-folder 12/41)
  - Crystal Springs Lake, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 12/42)
  - Cuba, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12/43)
  - Cubans in U.S., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12/44)
  - Cuprum, Idaho, 1961 (Box-folder 12/45)
  - Cups, 1962 (Box-folder 12/46)
  - Cypress Gardens, 1962 (Box-folder 12/47)
  - Dairy, 1963 (Box-folder 12/48)
  - Dairy--Alpenrose, 1960; 1964 (Box-folder 12/49)
  - Dairy--Mayflower Co., 1960; 1962-1963 (Box-folder 12/50)
  - Dairy Princess, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - The Dalles, 1962 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Damascus, Or., 1962 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Dams
    - Bonneville, 1960 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Bull Run, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Crooked River, 1963 (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Hells Canyon, 1961 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Hill Creek, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Ice Harbor, 1962 (Box-folder 13/9)
    - John Day, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Lost Creek, 1963 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Mayfield, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Mt. Sheep, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Nez Perce, 1969-1961 (Box-folder 13/14)
    - Oahe, 1962 (Box-folder 13/15)
    - Pelton, 1963 (Box-folder 13/16)
    - Portage, 1962 (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Priest Rapids, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/18)
    - Rocky Reach, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Round Butte, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Wanapum, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/21)
  - Dance
    - Ballet, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 13/22)
    - Ballets de Madrid, 1964 (Box-folder 13/23)
    - China Doll Review, 1964 (Box-folder 13/24)
    - Dance, 1964 (Box-folder 128/3)
    - Dancers, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 13/25)
    - Folk dancing, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/26)
    - Japanese, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 13/27)
    - Popcycles, 1964 (Box-folder 13/28)
    - Scotch, 1960 (Box-folder 13/29)
    - Square Dance, 1964 (Box-folder 13/30)
    - Sultan's Harem Dancers, 1964 (Box-folder 13/31)
  - Days Creek, 1963 (Box-folder 13/32)
  - Deaf, 1962 (Box-folder 13/33)
  - Delta Dome, 1964 (Box-folder 13/34)
  - Delta Park, 1962 (Box-folder 13/35)
  - Democratic convention, 1964 (Box-folder 13/36)
  - Democratic convention, 1964 (Box-folder Oversize B1/7)
  - Democratic Party, 1964 (Box-folder 13/37)
  - Democratic Party--Multnomah County, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 13/38)
  - Democratic Party--Woman of the year, 1963 (Box-folder 13/39)
  - Demonstrations, 1964 (Box-folder 13/40)
  - Dental Health Week, 1963 (Box-folder 13/41)
  - De Poe Bay, Or., 1961 (Box-folder 13/42)
  - Deschutes River, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 13/43)
  - Devers Eye Clinic, 1963 (Box-folder 13/44)
  - Diamond Lake, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Dieringer's Frozen Foods--Fire, 1961 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Disasters--Atomic energy, 1964 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Disasters--Boulders, 1964 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Disasters--Chemical plant explosion, 1964 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Discotheque, 1964 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Tuberculosis, 1964 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Disneyland, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Divers (see also Skin Divers), 1961 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Diving bell, 1960 (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Docks--Portland, 1963 (Box-folder 14/11)
  - Dog racing, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - Dolls, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 14/13)
  - Dow Chemical Co.--Klalama, WA, 1962 (Box-folder 14/14)
  - Drake Lumber Co., 1960 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - Drama, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 14/16)
  - Dredges, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 14/17)
  - Dreyfus, Louis Co., 1962 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - Drills, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 14/19)
  - Drought, 1964 (Box-folder 14/20)
  - Drought, 1961 (Box-folder 14/21)
  - Drugs--Holgate Farms, 1963 (Box-folder 14/22)
  - Drydocks, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 14/23)
  - Dunham Printers, 1961 (Box-folder 14/24)
  - Duraflake Co., 1961 (Box-folder 14/25)
  - Earthquake--Alaska, 1964 (Box-folder 14/26)
  - Earthquake--California, 1961 (Box-folder 14/27)
  - East Bank Esplanad, 1963 (Box-folder 14/28)
  - East Bank Esplanade, 1963 (Box-folder Oversize B1/8)
  - East Lake, 1962 (Box-folder 14/29)
  - Eastport Plaza, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 14/30)
  - Easter, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 14/31)
  - Edwards Air Force Base, 1964 (Box-folder 14/32)
  - Edwards Furniture Store, 1961 (Box-folder 14/33)
  - Eggs, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 14/34)
  - Election--Ballots, 1964 (Box-folder 14/35)
  - Elections, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 14/36)
  - Electronic brain, 1964 (Box-folder 14/37)
  - Electronic Specialty Company, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 14/38)
  - Elevators, 1961 (Box-folder 14/39)
  - Elk Lake, 1960 (Box-folder 14/40)
  - England, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 14/41)
  - Enerjet, 1961 (Box-folder 14/42)
  - Rentals, 1964 (Box-folder 14/43)
  - Esco Corp., 1962 (Box-folder 14/44)
  - Escort Beauty Shop, 1962 (Box-folder 14/45)
  - Eskimos, 1963 (Box-folder 14/46)
  - Estacada, Or., 1962 (Box-folder 14/47)
  - Eugene, Or., 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 15/1)
  - Equitable Savings and Loan Association, 1961 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Explosions, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - Explosions--Portland, 1961 (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Pacific Livestock, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - Eyes, 1962 (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Fair--Clackamas County, 1964 (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Fair--Multnomah County, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Fair--New York World's, 1964 (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Fair--West Linn, 1964 (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Fairview Homes, 1961 (Box-folder 15/11)
  - Fallout shelters, 1961 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Fanno Creek, 1961 (Box-folder 15/13)
  - Fans--Riot, undated (Box-folder 15/14)
  - Farm machinery, 1963 (Box-folder 15/15)
  - Farmers market, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 15/16)
  - Farms, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 15/17)
  - Farms, 1964 (Box-folder 128/4)
  - Ferns, undated (Box-folder 15/18)
  - Ferry--Buena Vista, 1963 (Box-folder 15/19)
  - Ferry--Columbia River, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 15/20)
  - Ferry--Columbia River, 1962 (Box-folder 128/6)
  - Ferry--Puget Sound, 1962 (Box-folder 15/21)
  - Fine Arts Pavilion, 1962 (Box-folder 15/22)
  - Fashion, 1961 (Box-folder 128/5)
  - Fashions, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 15/23)
  - Fashions, 1963 (Box-folder 15/24)
  - Fashions, 1964 (Box-folder 15/25-26)
  - Fires
    - Alabama, 1963 (Box-folder 16/1)
    - California, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Canada, 1962 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Florida, 1963 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Minnesota, 1964 (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Nevada, 1962 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - New Jersey, 1963 (Box-folder 16/7)
    - New York, 1962 (1853); 1964 (Box-folder 16/8)
    - Oregon, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Portland, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Portland, 1962 (Box-folder 16/11-13)
    - Portland, 1963 (Box-folder 16/14)
    - Portland, 1964 (Box-folder 16/15)
    - Washington State, 1961 (Box-folder 16/16)
  - Fire--Arsonist, undated (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Fire Belles, 1963 (Box-folder 16/18)
  - Fire Boat, 1969-1962 (Box-folder 16/19)
  - Fire Department--Nerve Center, undated (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Fire Department--Learning fire (Parkrose's first school), 1962 (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Fire Department--Toy and Joy Makers, 1961 (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Fire engines, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Fire hydrant, 1961 (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Fire--Infrared fire detection unit, 196? (Box-folder 17/6)
  - Fire fighters, 19662-1963 (Box-folder 17/7)
  - Fire men, undated (Box-folder 17/8)
  - Fire--Portland, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 128/7)
  - Fire--Portland, 1964 (Box-folder Oversize B/2)
  - Fireplaces, 1962 (Box-folder 17/9)
  - Fireworks, 1960-1961; 1964 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - Fire stations, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - Fish
    - Fish, 191-19626 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Anchovies, 1960 (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Bass, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Clams, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 17/15)
    - Eggs, 1961 (Box-folder 17/16)
    - Halibut, 1962 (Box-folder 17/17)
    - Lobsters, 1961 (Box-folder 17/18)
    - Octopus, 1963 (Box-folder 17/19)
    - Perch, 1961 (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Porpoise, 1963 (Box-folder 17/21)
    - Sailfish, 1961 (Box-folder 17/22)
    - Salmon, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 17/23)
    - Seals, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 17/24)
    - Sharks, 1962 (Box-folder 17/25)
    - Shrimp, 1960 (Box-folder 17/26)
    - Smelt, 1962 (Box-folder 17/27)
    - Squid, 1964 (Box-folder 17/28)
    - Starfish, 1962 (Box-folder 17/29)
    - Steelhead, 1962 (Box-folder 17/30)
    - Sturgeon, 1962 (Box-folder 17/31)
    - Trout, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 17/32)
    - Whales, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 17/33)
    - Fishing, 1963 (Box-folder 17/34)
    - Nets, undated (Box-folder 17/35)
  - Flag, 1963 (Box-folder 128/)
  - Flags, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 17/36)
  - Flagpole sitter, 1960 (Box-folder 17/37)
  - Floods
    - Floods, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Columbia River, 1961 (Box-folder 18/2)
    - Idaho, 1961 (Box-folder 18/3)
    - New York State, undated (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Oregon, 1962 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Florida--Key West, 1962 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Flowers
    - Flowers, 1961 (Box-folder 18/7)
    - Begonias, undated (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Camellias, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Chrysanthemum, undated (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Clemantis, 1964 (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Colchicum, 1961 (Box-folder 18/12)
    - Cyclamen, 1961 (Box-folder 18/13)
    - Daffodils, 1961 (Box-folder 18/14)
    - Dahlias, 1961 (Box-folder 18/15)
    - Dogwood, 1961 (Box-folder 18/16)
    - Fuchsia, 1961 (Box-folder 18/17)
    - Geraniums, 1961 (Box-folder 18/18)
    - Hydrangeas, 1961 (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Iris, 1961 (Box-folder 18/20)
    - Ivy, 1962 (Box-folder 18/21)
    - Lillies, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 18/22)
    - Magnolias, 1961 (Box-folder 18/23)
    - Orchids, 1961 (Box-folder 18/24)
    - Pansies, 1961 (Box-folder 18/25)
    - Rhododendron, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 18/26)
    - Roses, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 18/27)
    - Skimmia, 1961 (Box-folder 18/28)
    - Tulips, 1961 (Box-folder 18/29)
  - Flubber, 1963 (Box-folder 18/30)
  - Fog--Medford, 1963 (Box-folder 18/31)
  - Folk dancing, undated (Box-folder 18/32)
  - Food--Assistance, 1961 (Box-folder 18/33)
  - Food processsing--Bird's Eye, 1962 (Box-folder 18/34)
  - Formosa (Taiwan), 1962 (Box-folder 18/35)
  - Forest Grove, Or.--"Oregon Kid Gang", 1961 (Box-folder 18/36)
  - Fire fighters, 1961 (Box-folder 18/37)
  - Windstorm, 1963 (Box-folder 18/38)
  - Fort Lauderdale, Fla.--Easter vacation, 1961 (Box-folder 18/39)
  - Fort Stevens, Or., 1961 (Box-folder 18/40)
  - Fort Vancouver, Wash.--Historical museum, 1962 (Box-folder 18/41)
  - Fought and Co., 1962 (Box-folder 18/42)
  - Fountains, 1964 (Box-folder 18/43)
  - Fountains--Firemen's Memorial, 1961 (Box-folder 18/44)
  - Fountains--Washington Park, 1960 (Box-folder 18/45)
  - Four H Club, 1963 (Box-folder 18/46)
  - France, 1962-1963; 1964 (Box-folder 18/47)
  - France--World War I, TV news program, 1964 (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Fred Meyer, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Fred Meyer--Bowling, 1962 (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Freedom Center, Inc., 1961 (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Freeways--Portland, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 19/5)
  - Frogs, 1960 (Box-folder 19/6)
  - Fuel cell, 1963 (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Furniture, 1964 (Box-folder 19/8)
  - Fruit and Flower Nursery, 1961 (Box-folder 19/9)
  - Furs, 1963 (Box-folder 19/10)
  - Gama Goat--U.S. Marines, 1964 (Box-folder 19/11)
  - Gambling, 1961 (Box-folder 19/12)
  - Garbage, 1963 (Box-folder 19/13)
  - Garbage can, 1963 (Box-folder 19/14)
  - Garden Home--Community Methodist Church, undated (Box-folder 19/15)
  - Garden show, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 19/16)
  - Gardens, 1961 (Box-folder 19/17)
  - Gas Company Building, 1960 (Box-folder 19/18)
  - Gas explosion--Copenhagen, Denmark, 1964 (Box-folder 19/19)
  - Gas lights, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 19/20)
  - Gas--Northwest Natural Gas Company, 1961 (Box-folder 19/21)
  - Gas--Oregon, 1961 (Box-folder 19/22)
  - Gas Pipeline, 1961 (Box-folder 19/23)
  - Gas price war, 1961 (Box-folder 19/24)
  - Gazebos, 1962 (Box-folder 19/25)
  - Geese, 1961 (Box-folder 19/26)
  - General Extension Division, 1962 (Box-folder 19/27)
  - Georgia-Pacific, 1961 (Box-folder 19/28)
  - Gerber Legendary Blades, 1964 (Box-folder 19/29)
  - Gerber Reservoir, 1961 (Box-folder 19/30)
  - Germany, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 19/31)
  - Geysers, 1960 (Box-folder 19/32)
  - Ghana, 1961 (Box-folder 19/33)
  - Girl mariners, 1964 (Box-folder 19/34)
  - Girl Scouts, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 19/35)
  - Girl Scouts--Brownies, 1962 (Box-folder 19/36)
  - Girl Scouts--Mariners, 1961 (Box-folder 19/37)
  - Glacier Peak, 1961 (Box-folder 19/38)
  - Gladstone, Or., 1963 (Box-folder 19/39)
  - Glass, 1963 (Box-folder 19/40)
  - Glasses, 1964 (Box-folder 19/41)
  - Globe Dock and Elevator Co., 1960 (Box-folder 19/42)
  - Go-karts, 1961 (Box-folder 19/43)
  - Golf course, 1963 (Box-folder 19/44)
  - Golf course, 1963 (Box-folder Oversize B1/9)
  - Gonzaga University, 1961 (Box-folder 19/45)
  - Goodwill Industries, 1962 (Box-folder 19/46)
  - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company, 1962 (Box-folder 19/47)
  - Government Camp, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 19/48)
  - Gran storage bin, 1961 (Box-folder 19/49)
  - Grandma cookies, 1962 (Box-folder 19/50)
  - Granite, Or., 1961 (Box-folder 19/51)
  - Grapefruit (Gladys Canfield), undated (Box-folder 19/52)
  - Grave markers, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 19/53)
  - Graysons Store, 1961 (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Gresham, Or., 1961 (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Grocery store--Tuck Lung, 1963 (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Guilds Lake Industrial Park, 1961 (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Guns, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Gypsies, 1962 (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Hailstones, 1964 (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Haircuts, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Haiti, 1962 (Box-folder 20/9)
  - Haley's Foods, Inc., 1961 (Box-folder 20/10)
  - Halloween, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 20/11)
  - Hands, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 20/12)
  - Handcuffs, 1961 (Box-folder 20/13)
  - Handwriting, 1964 (Box-folder 20/14)
  - Harbor Patrol, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 20/15)
  - Harps, Irish, 1962 (Box-folder 20/16)
  - Harvey Aluminum Co., 1963 (Box-folder 20/17)
  - Haseltine, J.E. and Co., 1961 (Box-folder 20/18)
  - Hats, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 20/19)
  - Hawaii, 1964 (Box-folder 20/20)
  - Hay rides, 1961 (Box-folder 20/21)
  - Haystack Rock, 1962 (Box-folder 20/22)
  - Heart, 1960; 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 20/23)
  - Haceta Head, 1961 (Box-folder 20/24)
  - Helicopter, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 20/25)
  - Hells Canyon, 1961 (Box-folder 20/26)
  - Heppner, Or., 1961 (Box-folder 20/27)
  - Highland Games, 1964 (Box-folder 20/28)
  - Highlander, 1963 (Box-folder 20/29)
  - Highways
    - Highways, 1964 (Box-folder 20/30)
    - Baldock Freeway, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 20/31)
    - Banfield Expressway, 1963 (Box-folder 20/32)
    - Capitol, 1962 (Box-folder 20/33)
    - Eastbank Freeway, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 20/34)
    - Freeway, 1964 (Box-folder Oversize B1/10)
    - Freeways--Interstate 205, undated (Box-folder 20/35)
    - Freeways--Interstate 205, 1964 (Box-folder 128/9)
    - Freeways--Lake Oswego, 1964 (Box-folder 20/36)
    - Freeways--McKenzie, 1962 (Box-folder 20/37)
    - Freeways--Mt. Hood, 1964 (Box-folder 20/38)
    - Minnesota, 1962 (Box-folder 20/39)
    - Oregon, 1960; 1964 (Box-folder 20/40)
    - Oregon Coast--U.S. 101, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 20/41)
    - Pacific, 1961 (Box-folder 20/42)
    - Pacific Cascade, 1962 (Box-folder 20/43)
    - U.S. 30, undated (Box-folder 20/44)
    - U.S. 58, 1961 (Box-folder 20/45)
    - U.S. 99E, 1961 (Box-folder 20/46)
    - U.S. 99W, 1961 (Box-folder 20/47)
    - Willamette Valley, 1960 (Box-folder 20/48)
    - Signs, 1961 (Box-folder 20/49)
    - Stadium Freeway, 1962 (Box-folder 20/50)
  - Hiking, 1963 (Box-folder 20/51)
  - Hillcrest School, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 20/52)
  - Hillsboro--High School Band, 1961 (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Holiday on Ice, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Holladay Park, 1963 (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Holly, 1962 (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Holy Name Nuns, 1960 (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Home furnishings, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Home Improvement Show, 1964 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Home show, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Home of the Week, 1964 (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Homemaker of Tomorrow, 1964 (Box-folder 21/10)
  - Homes, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 21/11-12)
  - Hood Canal Bridge, 1961 (Box-folder 21/13)
  - Hood River, Or., 1961 (Box-folder 21/14)
  - Horse racing--Kentucky Derby, 1961; undated (Box-folder 21/15)
  - Horse racing, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 21/16)
  - Hospitals
    - Crestview Convalescent Center, 1964 (Box-folder 21/17)
    - Dammasch State, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 21/18)
    - Emanuel, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 21/19)
    - Good Samaritan, 1963 (Box-folder 21/20)
    - Milwaukie, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 21/21)
    - Morningside, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 21/22)
    - Ostepathic, 1962 (Box-folder 21/23)
    - Portland Sanitorium, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 21/24)
    - Providence, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 21/25)
    - St. Vincent's, 1963 (Box-folder 21/26)
    - Shriners, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 21/27)
    - T.B., 1963 (Box-folder 21/28)
    - West Hills Convalescent Center, 1963 (Box-folder 21/29)
  - Hotels
    - Benson, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Campbell Court, 1961 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Cosmopolitan, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Hawaiian Village, 1961 (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Hilton, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 22/5-6)
    - Hoyt, 1963 (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Milwaukie, Or.--Former Spencer School, undated (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Perkins, 1961 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Portland Hotel (circa 1890), 1963 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Sheraton, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 22/11)
  - House--Demolition, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 22/12)
  - House moving, 1962 (Box-folder 22/13)
  - Houses (see also Homes), 1961-1964 (Box-folder 22/14)
  - Houses--Alaska, 1960 (Box-folder 22/15)
  - Houses--Keil--Aurora Colony, 1963 (Box-folder 22/16)
  - Huckleberries, 1963 (Box-folder 22/17)
  - Hunting, 1962 (Box-folder 22/18)
  - Hurricanes, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 22/19)
  - Hyannis Point, Mass., 1961 (Box-folder 22/20)
  - Hyster Equipment Co., 1962 (Box-folder 22/21)
  - Ice, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 22/22)
  - Ice arena, 1963 (Box-folder 22/23)
  - Ice Follies, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 22/24)
  - Ice skating, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 22/25)
  - Incinerator, 1963 (Box-folder 22/26)
  - India, 1964 (Box-folder 23/1)
  - Indians, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 23/2)
  - Indians--Hopi, 1961 (Box-folder 23/3)
  - Indians--Kalisepp, 1962 (Box-folder 23/4)
  - Indians--Klamath, 1961 (Box-folder 23/5)
  - Indians--Warm Springs, 1962 (Box-folder 23/6)
  - Indian artifacts, 1962 (Box-folder 23/7)
  - Indian Center, 1961 (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Indonesia, 1964 (Box-folder 23/9)
  - Induction Center, 1962 (Box-folder 23/10)
  - Insect, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 23/11)
  - International Business Machines (IBM), 1962 (Box-folder 23/12)
  - International Highland Games, 1963 (Box-folder 23/13)
  - International Woodworkers Assoc., 1961 (Box-folder 23/14)
  - Irons, 1961 (Box-folder 23/15)
  - Iron Firemen, 1961 (Box-folder 23/16)
  - Irrigation, 1964 (Box-folder 23/17)